The in.
The
in.
The in the in.
The in.
The in the. The
bad writer to think some good style
my the magination I think is
a burnt out of the bed where Thank you very
much oh it's not really there's room to
be
a little pay I want to wear won't be in the
shinai are you on the water like turtle
was. One hour she is going. To the and
all. Aware of the water electric the
you know the killing was the air
so I have how do you close the
link. Were you taking the real me
you the stupid the sick and the still over
the banks of the and what do I look like
well you look very advanced the
Mideast. I want to very quickly
how to do it if you're right you're right
on time we almost didn't get here I was
doing was one dream we had to wait
for the Dr underwear I brought
a friend Mr Ronnie. This
is me let me get you
a chair no no no never mind
I'll sit in the bleachers with.
You were you going to be
a writer too I hope to be someday.
This lecture should help you
a great deal he's
a great. Course he gets
most of his ideas from me.
Excuse me you're sitting in my seat.
Anybody sitting here their plan planners
and what is out there tonight. Well then
why did you make me move. And I
don't think. I thank you for that
as I thought this you. Guess
because it might be not now that.
Last year. A
lot of allowed to. Understand
that most of your whole all sorts of
jobs during the day and yet you've been
studying the technique of writing in the
now you're ready to take your brain in the
hand and go out conquer the world. You
know I'm hardly the person to tell you how
to write because I don't follow any rules
today the writer is asked to keep one eye
on the bestseller list the other one.
That's divided along and that makes for
dishonest. I must confess I have been
guilty of this dishonesty too but now that
I've made my position secure
I'm going to try to write
a really good book No More bestseller
but something that I hope will be
a piece of great writing.
Good writing fine writing is
here and here the dictionary is filled
with all the words you need but unless the
mind and the heart find those words for
you you'd better leave them in the
dictionary he's so brilliant. Because
a writer fundamentally must believe
in himself that's half the battle.
I like to interrupt my little thought for
a moment to say that I'm going to be in
a position to help somebody here
in this class. Beginning tomorrow
I'm going to need
a secretary I already placed the request
with the university placement Yoro and the
man or woman whoever qualifies will get the
job that's very nice of you but the lot
of them well it's not
a big job but the surroundings will be
wholesome and you'll be able to serve your
apprenticeship under someone who's already
established well so much for that I
remember when I wrote my first.
Of a lot of work and. Lived in
a little back room all the while consoling
myself that I was. So you're really
going to work on water Well I was offered
the job by his personnel manager I've had
a lot of weird stories about on
a lot of very weird stories about anything
and I laugh now to talk with actually
inspiring did you realize I've
been here five years well in that
a little too long for anyone my ambition
whereas Mr Waterbury there was work. When
his personnel manager said in his
apartment apartment Well you can't expect
a writer to work in an office Mr Harris I
want to write and I think you can show me
how who knows where you are with the money
I might even be autographing copies of
my own book in one of
your books. By taking
a course. And getting paid for it at the
same time I'm going to miss you oh no you
won't after
a week you won't even know I've gone
through the good luck anyway where I could
make
a big speech but I think you know how I
feel about everything you've been wonderful
to. Understand it's.
Called me sometime why do we like
to know how you're getting on
a card you to night after I get the job.
Out there was one apartment Well
you can back up going around.
Smart guy with
a bag. Get up man. Anything drive these
days. Thank you for another
one word this out of my just one word much
about the ride on the job then ride my
license in the protecting
a lady in about an hour you know I. Is
he
a big guy six feet or less I'll cut him down
I didn't there was no words but nothing
. Are you sure he can find to the right
right then I know that. I remember the just
so much adult about Bill Lawry are sure
it is a I got
a bigger mouth and he's got. I've come
to my things and what are your direction
Evidently he has not followed
me till now that I want to
take all the things out of that saw and
put them into that that you know. No
no no not for Dr.
It's Come in come right in. That's
been to one of various former
secretaries she quit the smartest
wanted to do. This is my nick.
And how it's one a very
gave that to her as
a Christmas months. My
typewriter. Well that was sort
of
a new you but it's. My own fault we as
she brought her own Aujourd'hui. My
pot she she cooked once in a
while in my bed but she drank
a little. My cigarette stopped she smoked
too my big stick so we had germs in the
library. You'll find the tests.
Good bye. Good thing you didn't open
your mouth. Thank you come along
Bill don't know what your in. And what
can I do for you this this is your new
secretary Oh yes you're from the Kilbride
Yes I say look he knocked over Obama they
go all over the cockpit and it's going to
be hard to get out to we do try cleaning
it up please Mary not me the landlady says
I'm not to clean up anymore I just do my
regular work and get out of here which is
nice and tell thank you very much say
you're going to work out by Iranian I'm an
expert at this sort of thing curiously
cleaned up about six of my money to claw and
some rugs and this is the stuff you've been
using lately here and this is the woman
it was the woman who did it was an accident
you better just let the landlady see
that you'll have
a hundred dollars for damages to your rent
that's more than last month's I've got
some of my good looks why don't you work
on the rug and I'll work on your dress Why
don't you to work on the rug and I'll work
on her dress I was on my day I work on
the kitchen if you like hot dogs occasionally
yes prime we'll have them for lunch
and for dinner we'll have lunch dinner but
I haven't even been in if you guess what
your name Stephanie Gaylord What do your
friends call you Steve all that settles it
I think she should be hired How are
you enjoying one hundred twenty words
a minute you do laundry. My own generally
what is going to happen learn to do silk
shirts one hundred twenty
a minute I'll do the cooking and listen
if he has to know I live next door he
hasn't been there since July that's because
I have no kitchen but we do we share
our kitchen on
a co-operative basis he cooks and eats.
You know when I went to school together
I wasn't in the garden and he was in the
eighth grade and I went to high school he
was still in kinda guy and then
I studied piano and became
a character and every Waterbury
books and what were you and. I was
a chorus girl who studied piano and was
very bitter about the world why did you
work for me I was secretary to Charles
Harris he owns the bookstores all over the
country and how is this to Waterbury his
latest novel doing second only to the
Bible like. You married Steve Well remember
these Ronnie I'm not interested in
whether or not Gaylord is married.
My biscuits are burning. I've had married
secretaries before and the husbands were
a little troublesome they were murdered.
His working hours are very peculiar.
I think we've done
a good job I had such. A job
would be like oh today was an
unusual but after this will be no
more distractions. We're going to
work in an atmosphere of dignity and cost.
It's your bookmaker. Mary
that man here again I heard.
How much do I owe this time eleven bucks
don't you give me no more of your tips for
next time out time I'll be dragging along.
Well or what are we going two hundred
seventy eight and
a buck for you. And
you are I'll have to well you mine till
next week you want to wager today well I
have looked them over
yet but I'll give you
a call and no more fifty cent
that's the boss don't like.
Where was it you were telling me that
everything here was dignified and cultural Oh
yes now Steve about your other duties. I.
Did you just have an interview with
my daughter Mary Hastings about
a secretarial job well yes it's.
I have a message for you. It's just
a lot of very I don't think I want this
job well why not live when you spoke at
class last evening when everything seemed
so so refreshing and when I read your
novels but they were filled with such
quality and high purpose and I'm afraid all
that spoiled. No harsh words no hard
feelings just. Just get somebody you
know well if that's the way
you feel Miss Gaylord.
Are you walking out on all in Waterbury
don't back the girl or work for me Ronnie
just call the agency and get another girl
now you know you don't mean that we both
like this one are you going to let me out
of here do I have to call the police.
There Already. I came from the cookbook so
Mrs Reeves I just mailed you
a check this morning oh you always do
that knowing full well that I only lived
downstairs and damaged
this month or it's been
a very very uneventful month
oh the cop again. Makes
the. This wish. And
this is back up here because we're the
whole country Mrs Riis if you'll excuse me
and screaming just outside the door our
new secretary Well yes yes you're being
hard about it miscarry Laura has just been
engaged Oh too bad for the purpose of
the movie popping up stairs but just
fill your every required with well
unfortunately Mrs Reeves that the job is
just unfair but I want you to be ready
wait for me.
For the shot and I want you to be the favors
that would work very hard you do. How
do you do about how I've kept Felicia came
to some point to get into the movies not
who did you realize you were on
I don't tell me let me guess.
They do piss off course not Felicia's
addition to being a secretary is
a very good actors aren't you do you
take off your coat next to the.
She's got a lot of talent there
I thought you think so I was
a model back in Texas
but I came out here for
a career daddy's financing me
a friend of your know my father objects
police you could play the heroine in your
next novel when it made good movie she
could do that it was a heroine that it's
a girl from the south.
From the Sal how to keep.
She's trying to hook a rich
man she's insincere and
a moron. But what's worrying Well
I'm not so worried about being
insincere but as for being
a mole Ron Don't worry about
that you could act like
a moron couldn't you do you could try.
All I'm going to grammatic school
maybe they can teach me to be a MO Ron if
you studied hard enough yeah it'd take
a lot of work this reads I haven't even
started my novel yet and it doesn't look as
if I'm going to have I'm continually
interrupted Well we'll even let YOU word Oh
Ronnie I'm having
a party for fifty guests tonight and I'm
expecting you to entertain far as they
know is it informal or shall I be.
If you don't get data tainted by
pop is that your right. Where I'm
off to the show you haven't got
a chance. You
know ever since her husband died left
there's seven buildings she's been
a peeping tom Muncie but you I prefer
like you look I say don't worry because I
just want to cause
a scene in front of your land like I'm
releasing the one I. Make the stuff you want
to get down to with
the and.
The and.
The man. At the end.
The I'm going to. Call it. Oh.
I'm my new novel. That's often
out tomorrow morning at ten
o'clock. The in.
Soon to be he's
a debating the last was. Always I remember
I'm last year's love I
was baking a cake of
a something called the US about how to
start the dictation and I couldn't go back
until it was through dictating at three
o'clock in the morning we sat down the
chocolate covered ashes. I see
you at ten o'clock.
Hello hello Steve I couldn't wait for
you to call me so I'm calling you I was
a job well I have to make an
adjustment to know if. Such an unusual
kind of
a job I can imagine. He he started
his novel today. Interesting
story well he didn't get very far into it
but I'm sure it's going to be wonderful
he seemed so excited about it. Let's
have dinner one night this week.
I'll call you the best not I have.
Money where you are bright and early this
morning at ten o'clock. Jerry think how
you look at me I see you've got your pair
good friends so poised the genius is
still dressing I make you potato
pancakes for lunch and he's in
a sour cream mood today if you need anything
ironed I'll be in the kitchen I heard
a report of one of the right. At sea.
When I leave off yesterday.
On my new novel Yeah.
Hello. Hello. I
know. Now why would anybody know
it's on my new novel or you. Make that
notes on my new novel by oh in
Waterbury that's good oh that's real
good not to think that's good I like that
chapter one general in production of
characters. Chapter two back
to Chapter two to Mark chapter
a day that's wow you sure you're not tired
this good or you say your name to the
telephone I I'm going to the beach with
them so if they're over here you don't
bring any home with you right away that's
Guy someplace nice like Santa Barbara the
anything you say. Don't
pay any attention to
him he's just trying to make you jealous
jealous but what makes you think I'm even
interested in him you know for
a secretary who has just been given the
day off you're awfully annoyed I know I
could have done annoyed or I just don't
want to sit here doing nothing I came here
to work and I came here to do nothing and
now I'm working Look if you get paid for
idleness grappa to pull.
There goes another one.
It's. Look I'd like to ask you
a quick yes does Mr Waterbury
intend to write a book that's
a very interesting question one a very is
a genius what he's doing right now
incubating exactly and when we go through
a move like this a great book
comes out of that he does
a lot of writing tonight why honey you're
general or you don't I don't even know
who missed
a lot of very disappointed I'm not
even sure I want to of course not it's
. It's they can you tell me what I'm
doing with everything here let me have
a time when you get so many wrinkles in
it we tried sixty laundry but he still
likes my work best These are good shirts
weren't good chairs you know I just
thought of what I'm going out of my mind
was when I went to night school for
a whole year to learn to be a
writer and here I am doing
a guy's laundry. Oh it's not done yet.
Hello. This is only what about I want
you to be here tomorrow morning at nine
o'clock I finally got the idea thank
you. You know I like that idea
I don't think there's
a heart and there can be
the never. It's from. The
book. The IT.
Was a warning all the code on the
pack to be here in just a minute but
a burger which you can use my weekly for
the race to the road if you're behind
Never mind it's while I was walking the
first time to the back and wait till after
the service but I got what I got out of
the long you complaining about being paid
to go to the races come. Into the in.
Somebody who's got it's well so far this
job has cost me eighty three dollars I
don't worry I'll get that back why should
you I gambled and I lost well cruising is
good for the so we have the
three best souls in town.
The if the.
Morning morning they be called
a speed the plane these thirty five minutes
rule for you calling Las Vegas to get
back eighty three dollars on the gas I
can't go to Las Vegas with you are you
objecting to being paid while working. I
don't think I'm going to want to watch the
new much longer Mr Watt up there and almost
even taken on a half a fly if your T.V.
Paying back your home in time for
dinner put tons of money in the full.
Fare when you're trying to write in your
full of adult dollars that they want to
because I just told
a girl here with that coming. Your way or
what is your point our way or the hard
way are why are the Air Con Air kids
and seventy year low to stand in our
mind exactly nothing but
are we leaving this
a lot of media I'm stuck three thousand
but you said with Tess the midnight flag
will be another planet
to die let's hear from
a rabbi we're trying to
go I may or may not own
a girl that's going to require I stop working
for right it was going to be so must
look to her right Syria or they want to
do it I didn't do anything she didn't
mean it what are you creating about I'm
betting on crap. Everything was going to be
so intellectual. Her etc get a warning on
a letter or are you doing that on purpose
which is. Thank you you're doing all
right honey that's her point for point is
proud to make anything but crap. I was
going to need only literary
people. Per. Year right.
Ever saw the pay for the most make any
more crap understand I'll tell him when he
comes then keep your mind on the
dice. Seven holiday I. Know I'm
writing a novel to make
the world you know be
a honey eternal one curse. Goodness.
What's wrong keep your mind on
a dice when you're wrong. How dare
you speak to me like. The guy.
I'm going and I never want to see you again
you're. A cheap egotistical fraud your
whole existence is something I want no
part of I'm sorry I even met you because
you've spoiled something from. My
impressionable and now to bury the writer.
I want to talk. This game with you
can insidious it changes a person I'm
going to target. Why don't you put
a stop to all of this get them
to work. I guess I'm afraid.
I'm afraid I'm not the great writer
I started out. That I'm just
a commercial right oh no you. Didn't
you see how everyone at the university
treated you with. The don't
you read Mother Love Story to
going backwards backward. To your
last to know the story of the plan
one of the play Hamlet you
keep telling yourself you're
a baby or you'll be one if I find out
a love story when you
work for. Her I work for
a. Bank. I'm poor
again I just switched to seven.
I did not keep records tell you why the
taxes are going to be here in just one
minute why or don't worry we're going to
work let's do it at the beach house you
superstitious and he starts all his novels
at the beach I think how you like last
year's love. Well most of last year's love
with guns they're. Telling kids to type
but I'd hate to be
a nice idea and I would just stop teaching
the girl I'll be dictating today I might
be. Out of it take
this in outline form and then
I'll polish it up later yes it's
a lot of very. This is the story of
a successful novelist who began
to be morally and spiritually to
a girl came into his life and then the
whole world seemed changed in Siena one
night Rod delivering a lecture to
a short story that there were so many faces
looming up in front of him but he saw
only one interviews with
delicate exquisitely beautiful.
Without analogy arranged to make his
secretary because in that fleeting moment in
that single instant he knew he
was desperately in love with.
One day he asked her to go to the beach
house and work there because he he wanted
very much to tell her the way you felt but.
Elect the courage to write of Barry or
miss Gaylord when I'm working I don't
like to be the spirit. Or what. He wanted
very much to tell us how he felt that
he lacked the courage Oh oh yes.
Now here she was seated
before him tender fragile as
a pore he had looked around
a corner to corner and there she
was. What's the matter of. Pent up.
Beds continue. He was tempted to take her
up in his arms and sweep it to the summit
but he didn't he knew very little about
her yet there was nothing else he needed
to know and he strode up and down the room
dictating. He looked toward
a polka dot necktie What's
the matter with you nothing.
There was
a pocket that necktie. He
was impressed by the loveliness the
break air were so. Delicate and
a breathing living thing that made him
exalted and inspired he wanted to take her
in his arms and smother her with kisses
and drowned himself in the beauty of her
soul but he was
a car. Idea like if it had
possibilities suddenly he
threw caution to the wind
leaned over and kissed.
Noted in his arms and offered no desist.
Wordlessly that if you know that one
hundred silent embrace.
You've got the wrong girl Mr Waterbury
I'm really leaving you this kind of time
don't you want to try to get in touch
with me again I don't even want my salary
check you can say that for the next victim
if I ever see one of your books again.
And that.
Allo Allo son I just thought I'd card watch
and I make dinner for the three of us
and have seen those joints pop
over the years just quit Yeah
I'm dictating
a harmless little thing suddenly she
takes offense Franz me on the cars with
a hammer lock and works out Is she insane
well I'll call the agency and get in the
center of another girl about to get one of
like broiled chicken and that's what we
have for dinner don't call anybody
I'm not going to go to work for
a long time. Come
on come on when you get out of your so
I can watch these keys I'm composing
composing Now I haven't heard
a good song how do you look.
That's it to me that again.
Thank you very much. What
are you calling that thing.
I got
a call in my nose one thing it is not the
dog the filly I just want to hear the
quality.
God. You know.
Having.
Like to go another places
on. This is about zero.
Or zero gravity.
Showing you. Video on you.
All right just so that you
won't get
a piece of pie. I. Miss it
out of thirty one Friday
. Thirty one method
not the least of chicken.
Roast chicken happen your poker roast
neither roast at the pressure cooker no
little oh do you have
a dinner out to the bank or my you don't
think I'm going to this horrible mess.
I know he has a nice car you just
want to bury your mother for
a. Lot of that because my duties are starting
to take. In the kids Adami I want to
go home. I don't care if they
set fire to the home of.
A lot of going to. Be
going to tell them I have
a deal on you if you tell others
about it about it. Or want to.
Stop asking me silly questions I call you
on the phone she quit that she had some
nerve I don't hear a lot of the
secretary or capable officials in just
a few You're never did find
out what you could. Call the
agency and get another secretary I got
a better idea than do I want to. Where
you go and they are change about my
work better than I'm getting the
apartment at. What should happen that's
a very unfair question when I'm not
going to let a little thing like
a secretary throw me off balance
never in a million years I've got
a right to live two wonderful beautiful
exciting life I'm going to bump in time
a break from intensity and scope or you
know something Ronnie I'm glad this
happened I'm down. With.
One good and then use it.
All to be called she's
sorry she quit and she apologized for the
cab driver. That's what Steve will be
doing tomorrow having an apologizing but I
won't be here. One of my running working
for anyway I'm not afraid of her
what I like. A real lot of very
wealthy will take her out to dinner. With
a different one it's not going to
change my apron to be right back.
Or Brian detective agency. This is own
Waterbury Yeah look I want you to
shadow a girl for me.
Stephanie Gable. Have
a good time tonight OK I'm with
a gun and I'm welling ready because I
want to. Hear why where I like it here
because Haditha originally room. I'm
not joking you Bob Those are the icons
so I always say to Mr
want to carry There's
a gentleman who shall. Run
in when you take me to
a table and I'll join in just right
but don't leave a stone Elsie with
a check from your table for
a day when our call to. Determine
whether. You send me that method
is brand detective Devon is the name what
I have to find is the fact that's my job
is right over there with
a man whose name I don't find the Course
I do or write about shadowing both
him and I want to find out if they can
about it I think she's in love with your
wife no my secretary. But I want nobody
to know about it don't worry the way I
operate even you were. To take
a pass for it would be expensive. You
just finished taking a good job with
a year to get a passport up of
a pretty. Good job I will
take care of my trip. Yes
give me
a place. The
new.
The smoking. Folks
to. Smile. A little
Ronnie go talk to her mad
act of God. Good evening. Good evening.
You know him. He's my new barn and you
brought What's his name charm hair in
the book Santa at the use of
old. Is not so hot there to go
work for him this is Shakespeare out what
people might be able to get the big bang
her over to the combine. And the power
complimenting me for somebody with the
character. Of
a Jew qualified used to work for was out
there in the with her principals out with
her ex boss. About Alfie when we're
talking about Stephen her friend the
by not of this guy but here it's hard to
adjust the spy on me when you're not very
complimentary I happen to be an excellent
the it. When did you learn the dear.
Lord and even question you about me.
Only the novel question my dear if.
You didn't did you. Run
a minute stop looking at everything in one
big black was going to last so you have
a crime for
a bride to be by the bride going to
be married. When you don't want to
talk to her go to place
about chicken. Blood of
a glassful cold. Below.
The Heron was the route of their well
congratulations I just heard the good news
what good news about your marriage. May I
dance with. The bright side of the good
man. I'm not
a. Hero she decided to get
married with the wrong guy I'm
only going to dance are you going to
dictate a novel I want you to niceness of
a girl like you marry
a man to go to sleep for your information
I'm not marrying anyone oh well now I
respect you respect or
go decide not to get me.
Going back to work for this it's
a clear I'm going to the ground it could
be no. Doubt about your own job back
better terms not interested. I'll throw in
a bone marrow. List of what about you
talk about marriages there was something
cheap and vulgar. But own words about it
would have but you are the man that's for
the other girls I was. The one
to pay him back and that's
a bit bearable I would think that that
was my bar. This is me you're talking to
remember. Well I mean not
to live rough for. Him to.
What some might. Hear in my class
owning it was us were dancing in
the be dancing but I'm holding.
Like this trying to go rock through
also coming or rather be with the most
maddening man of
a man this is the speed of the
everything at the feet of the beach was
a mess but was too much of a
coward. He married me take
a chance. This is me the awesome
is beautiful with all I can say. I
love Yes Mary. Got chicken madame. And
your chicken the glad.
Well the World War or
the
another. Era looks lovely.
The night
without a hitch I really
do want to sit down have
a glass of broiled chicken.
Thank goodness I will. And.
The new in the pot.
They are the story of the
of only three. Of me don't
but I think I'll be running
a lot of menopause you might take me with
is not about. Who's going to take place
you want the plough saw.
The first. One to dance in the
universe.
Are you receiving the answer
tonight I think I will be
the
or one. Of the OR
or if the wise brains when one gets up in
the morning one never knows what one will
be doing the thing does one of the reader.
Or one of the all. And in
addition to the office
supplies please offer one Remington
electric typewriter for the hour.
At all. When.
The matter is anything wrong on what
a very just married street. Oh yes
he did I never thought she'd marry
him. I never thought he'd get.
Well.
Then gradually. May I be the first.
Or am I the first I'm not
a very wide awake Let's get some sleep
never go to the beach how long you've been
driving around Vegas and by. All of
those the police over the news she
decided to move it's a
good idea this is quite
a special free stories. That I've. Read.
Very well. I'm going to move it is I get
a room. Why don't you try the
bill in the door of the.
Bride or
a ladies' home. Or the in
the Mary. Thank you Mary.
Ellen. Maybe it's just.
Me the wedding breakfast. The getting
at me. When I know you're trying
to be helpful is that when
we try to be dumb Oh sure.
Say Steve be nice to me when you
use my only means of support.
For your point you made me
a question and now when it wasn't for
the moment and you do change your mind.
Never change your mind about human
interface nice thing and then.
Tell me where is the Free Will you're
looking for but not the business of the
people in the. Pocket that.
I think of right now.
Yes What can I do for you I have a bit of
a good work about it I'm afraid but what
a very can't be disturbed
just now he's. A little busy
My name is Devon would you tell him the
woman he's interested in got married.
And they all. Got
a minute. Ronnie what is it now there's
a fella was outside said his
name was destiny he had
a message for. Me He said the party
you were interested in got married
congratulations so did I I.
Don't think. You were interested in who got
married there's only one married girl.
You tell Mr Waterbury I want to see
right away and I'm Me Me Me. Here we
call you that affectionately. Now
what it is to cue the I don't
know your breath could carry was
working late they're married
now well this is why she might as well be
an old man just going to do for you Mrs
Reed I've got to read what I paid you the
rent on the first Mrs Reed I've had to
make a new rule this is not
a very good I don't take that chance
when you make that rule into moved in.
Downing you have to have four hundred eighty
five dollars in the bank I think so I
could do right now to check can I get this
thing straight into can understand how
my condo so low that six thousand for
the crap. Oh. And the two bucks for the
marriage right it was
rather have. A. Good Year.
Thank you Mrs whatever it is.
Already has been
a good she's loaded. It was an
explanation is in order you
don't hear me an explanation of
a damn thing I want to
explain. Or excuse me.
Oh oh congratulations we just
thank you Birdie. Thanks
a lot oh. We're going to come in and sit
down. Oh darling I want you to meet Mr
my publisher and Bertie This is
my wife it is so nice. Oh I'm not
thinking of prolonged running the whole no
are just going down to the beach Allison
when I thought I'd take my honey
with a good idea you know it's
a deadline that's got to be
made. So I have it ready.
Would you like
a drink. Gonna come over still eating the
same old birdies to me
about Ronnie she has
a body dies the crematorium debased
him slowly. You know funny cause
I was once Mr Waterbury
secretary. Thanks an
awful lot of for coming
Dick. DURBIN Thank you.
Darling I didn't make it you still accusing
the well I own twenty thousand dollars
due to the band drug against my next novel.
That mink coat Mrs Fulton had on that
when you gave her a book
meant nothing to me written
a bestseller and I was throwing money around
like water and always take it back and
give it to Mr payment on get you a hundred
make tiling I don't think I can afford
a hundred. Paying your rent broke did you
marry me for my money you know but I'm
beginning to think you married me some on
the lookout and let's get out if you want
never going to be alone here on
a perfect little mountain cabin away from
publishers and RAM ladies and setting
except you go to work. I promise you.
I want your work on this book for
my. Round of proud of this one big.
We're going about our speed down
a bit as getting those who want to marry
one of the special dinners. I'm afraid I
can't stay for dinner. Next greenbacks.
Big drop this expense How do you like the
book I'm actually trying to
write between the eyes on.
Just about the worst piece of drivel ever
read. If I were to publish this thought
it would ruin Fortunately I found another
book use misplaced but somehow it would
become right through of course
not every top like novelist has
a bad book at it how am I going to pay
back your money don't worry about that.
Sorry now I have some of that wonderful
man. I have on this it's so nice seeing you
again you like venison but I'm
afraid I got a very. Wrong I got
a very important. Well I'm very sorry I
was going to fix you one of my oldest.
Some other time. Back by me. By this.
Do you think. We've been right until we
married thirty or seven gonna do it so
maybe he's changed ever think about it.
Maybe he sees you through different eyes
talk like a four zero in the face of
your book is now being published by
a man who sees his wife in your arms on
every page this girl in there is thirty
when you are a child Brody meant nothing
to me he doesn't realize that he's still
a human being even if he
has a publisher and he's
a man. Let's get away
from here tonight. My.
Erwin you blame me don't you.
Not really even it's true so
distracting to have
a man swipe at the secretary to say
I'm going to try another book fast.
When I have to get up another
sector. So I'm fired is that it.
Will be better for both of us
about work by myself. To give you
a chance to work on your own
book. I'll make dinner.
Only. I finished my book.
Then I'd like to read it.
It's been on your dressing room
table for two weeks. When I
read it on the train don't bother. You
know now. You call and get tickets
for the train and Grania
wanted to get you in.
The air.
Over the border there L.O.L.
Significant tell me
a part of the station must have and I
thought. It must be lovely up at the cabin
the time of the year yet sitting on. A
lot of very original. Is laughable.
To you tell
a child that don't want to thank you for
your looking fine well four months of the
out alive none the worse for
it. Child I want you to do me
a favor this is I want latest book doesn't
like it I want you to read it and
let me know what you think about it I'll
try to be as objective as possible you
will be I know. That I have another
manuscript for you mind you finished it yes
that it was
a long uphill post. I've changed the title
so many times that I finally decided to
call it daunting and others on the
brink of its own haven't read it yet
although he hasn't had time he he's been
busy writing he couldn't concentrate on
and I'll be glad to read both. Thank you.
Advice but by telling.
Not the third floor but
a cap on one very prominent. How do you
do the employment service at me over
the only one very welcoming
Secretary. Snow. Who will follow me.
I know it's going to be so exciting
work is. Not the no I wish.
You know this it's
a rush come right down to dribble. All
Thank you so much you know I make my own
clothes. Come out in.
Just the name of the back I need back to
all I'm doubting this is doing you except
the street how do you do my husband
a lot of really and this is running out
next door neighbor how do you do can I get
you something to drink I have to learn to
be happy when I should say we had to and
we had to put up. If I could sit down.
With us for an appointment I
thought they knew our account.
Was that are.
Put up by those who bring their beer with
you big more comfortable. Over do you do
laundry machine boxes do shirts and socks
I don't want to do she looked down please
. How are you Ron handicapping the horses
recently bought yesterday at the two
women site a bus ride
on the schnoz a lot O.
And I think you can. Do you really hit
record of the job oh you want to be like
all these employees mink coat for
Christmas. But the big guns.
I wonder who she means I've got all
of this stuff you're all of those.
Who knew you were working late hour you
missed me back or not is. A room with
a girlfriend I haven't seen
this is. I'm afraid that I'll
be
a little too much for you right now when
you see several parts of my new and of the
most being friends and one sure you don't
speak right through to be stable daddy
did for six years once I had
a friend boyfriend we had no trouble.
Yes but I was your shorthand.
Sure of it and I don't like shorthand
you don't take shorthand well know
that this is strictly
a typing job. This is mostly
in short. I could learn it
all the grade. Wow guess
that let me out leave the
glass. Back there.
That would be the next point the next one
I told the agency to keep sending them
until we've said when.
How do you do it if apartment three
yes it is. Does Mr Owen run again in
here yes he does. I'm
going to Waterbury allow him to go to the
eighty percent. Don't come our way. If
you come in Miss O'Malley thank you. Won't
you sit down Mr Mallock Thank you oh
this is my right how do you do how do you
do. You take short and of course one
hundred twenty words in all what do you
speak french Mr Mallock the man that they
wanted him a piano he was
a bit of a shot at a ball
a. Rod that was in the ballet Are you
married by any time yes I am but the
divorce confinement I see when I'm
with you like you because you have
begun Oh thank you Steve shall we prepare
lunch and leave them alone I think they'd
like to get the work right.
Terribly digital work for
a writer before you know once about three
years ago but I'd rather not talk about
old one. Well he asked me to work
late one evening and began getting
a little fresh so I call the police all I
want to do is work I guess the purpose of
the brain is clear but he deserved
it don't you agree yes I do.
How about lunch Miss O'Malley
a lot over the Eton thank you and you
darling no thanks skip lunch today.
You were just living in this building the
doc and you'll get. There well received.
I have so. Oh how about negative
runs very I want you to
between
a bus stop move never the best of the fears
of Police do you think I'm fine with
the scour the mountain not only have an
hour or two to be the important member of
the family. I wouldn't want to know how
do you do you do the horrible running
a thing allow new secretary Yes he was just
tired and I was just tired but it's got
the right to Bob describing the business
to Scott and I went nice move together
with that next to each other just to be
able to look at those Sure does being in
a padded even move what do you know so
we're right back why didn't the radio
program called John's mother is not John's
mother sweetheart tell me. He's just
not
a good memory as we don't know John's
father objects John has no father. Poor
Dr. To the news that
a Russian spy stopped work on that radio
program your months neglect John Well I'm
in
a little trouble you see my secretary just
got married what on earth are you going
to do you know I don't know I can't help
you Sylvan you've been Yes You see I was
with the right of free Secretary before
you married me that's right you were
married with
a bomb and when to do it again why don't
you just say I've begun running give would
you get me some shorthand books and some
pencil How much do you think you'll be
giving me tonight while we may be working
most of the night but that's just ducky
I'm used to working at night by Dolly So
would you like I will come on. Thank you
Ron. All right there will be
a man after. I goes out
on the. Most to go I was
just poisoning the sea.
You know. You're going to really like
a deer hunter what your hand I don't
tolerate familiarity from anybody and I mean
anybody I went through and
a man's career and don't you forget it
Miss O'Malley you may have the day off why
don't you make it
a year but I haven't even begun yet that's
all right you could say just the same.
All right. What time tomorrow or when
your time Suit yourself. But I don't
understand about No All right thank you.
Now you're saying something about
poison. I make that I get first these
not robots I sound of footsteps
three people bank sound of
footsteps three people. There are
buying there are cries there are so I
am too shy rescreen Baron. Well
it's bedlam. John I'm in love with
your mother and tomorrow I
expect to be. John's going to be
a father and I'm the first to know.
I don't have to listen to mom.
But Father I'm older than you
are Johns all goodness father.
That's what I'd like to know. I don't know
but don't you I miss Waterbury I'm not
going to do anything.
And. Just turn up
a lot. Who's calling this is Giles
Harris thinking I'm sorry they got in
such
a late but I must talk to him they just
turned out the light where you keep quiet
This is their heart you know she's out for
the air and I don't know when she'll be
back and you'll hear me I said
they just turned out the lights.
The red light. I don't care what
you do. In the matter I'm going
to a hotel in case
you're interested. Go to
a hotel after all this is your apartment
knowledge is that you pay the rent money
what you think is that it's got. Oh man
you can't possibly be jealous of that
man up here but he's utterly. Wrong or
you're really hurt me for what do you say
that child Harris. The on the
scene he says we came back.
Terribly Laden and I don't like cross-examination
after all we're to act on human
beings and we should be with one another
don't smart of the way with pretty words
speed if you can see them. Yeah all right
and this is it but I only child parent
for one reason I took in
your manuscript he knows
a great many publishers three dollars to
make but they're stuck at the night you
are not with Harry and I knew he was
in love with you are all five years is
a long time and I was
a fool to begin to break it down I never
loved Charles Harris would you never love
me you must love the schoolgirl notion of
a popular novel I really try to play this
straight with this but I guess I made up
field
a mistake. I was in love with her
before I met you. Something in your
writing the tone the feeling the
quality appear to me so much that. I
used to imagine your books were written
just for me. I believe that the new
girl waited. And I was so caught up in the
I guess I would have married you that
night you like to think. If you had stepped
off that platform and asked me if I
would have married you just like that.
I put you way up there to steer you toward
it down in the cruelest way any woman
could. You want to call me an egotistical
fraud but what about you Stephanie
Gaylord one of you big guy had
finally waiting for you while.
The minuses was
a day of mourning and. Yes I know
Mr Harrison It was Friday. The
Morning. Certainly gave us this is
Mr Allen Mr literary pack How do you
do. So you are Stephanie
Gale. The Dons the.
Morning of life. This
McNally as head of the publishing house
in New York you flew down this morning
that's why I called you so late
last night we read your book was
a lot how long have you worked on
it. About five years I recommended
brought
a big belly was the first novel by not no
I didn't know you were going to show my
manuscript and. I couldn't do anything
else after reading it but the did you see
what this will do to oh my god is
all I've got to deal with. Rather
are ones the big guy in my family and has
not been turned down if this happens on
top of that it would just about
the story. He has to have
a sense of importance he's lost all faith
in Him You mean your husband would be in
a sense of competition with you you don't
understand the McNalley are ones in
trouble and this is why I have to help
him climb out of the Steve I thought you
wanted to write more than anything else
in the world to before I married him what
about Helen's manuscript to read.
This it isn't bad it's good
but it doesn't have
a this has this is great. You
very much stand on these
please and. I want to talk.
So.
When you look at this kitchen exam. Giving
your papa over is another try to give me
time to come up my own
apartment. So that's not.
Right let's try it again. John's
mother I've changed my mind
I don't like your sweetheart mother but
I like him that's all that matters John
as your son I refuse to approve the married
mother you're not marrying him I know
how does that sound thanks
man Mr Hastings I must say
you're distrusting. You know you shouldn't
be using Mr want to Barry's apartment or
Mr Waterbury secretary Mrs Waterbury isn't
here to get the program out why don't
you work in your apartment she will
work. And I want to work with. I'm
a dictator there why don't you
work. I don't work in men.
It's not a bedroom it's a
bachelor apartment my husband is
a hotel one of them is about to run or
is an apartment building she's going to
they're. All over the water Betty and
what can I do if you remember me
I'm definitely
a brand detective agency all. Over eight
hundred forty five dollars and sixty two
cent. Doing and delving into the Stepneygate
I'm married and we've been there
before and. Get rid of this
guy you want to call up
the police. You expect my
wife to do your laundry.
That's
a little large for you and Mrs
Waterbury. Can get out of here. But you.
Are taking dictation from somebody else.
I wouldn't you even if I did like your
problem. Stephanie and I know where she is
a way to pay this bill and I'll let you
know. Eight hundred forty five dollars and
sixty two cents Why don't you write him
a check. Number right
away here's the detailed
report it's very amusing to see I
have to show you at the same time.
What are you doing. Stephanie there any
chance of getting killed by me in.
Well maybe she got her old job back
working for him at his home what self
respecting girl worked for
a man at his home maybe should secretary
probably don't tell me about the secretary
he could tell you is
a ripple through the. Problem for many I'm
going to show her I want to grow this
tape but. I'm calling from it for
a lot of typing I don't care what
we don't care what long as you.
Do you take shorthand over it
of course how did twenty words
a minute. And. What did you
say your name was pigeon.
Her name is pigeon everybody says I'm like.
Where did you work before I'm just out
of secretarial school I think it would be
wonderful working for you Mr Bradbury You
see I hope to be
a writer myself and. Have you
ever been married Oh no never and
you have no objections to working the
weekend Oh not at all my time's completely
miles and you think Mr
Waterbury just one. Who's.
This is
a clay pigeon. I come from
I think I'll me Bill I
know just where to go I want
to take everything. Right.
Back but it's only. When
the mink coat I didn't get
a mink coat come into the bedroom. That's
a man Sure I mean they haven't you been
here before I came with the other one I got
a tab. Number needed to build a
new window and I'm going to do
a lot of hollering now. That's his former
secretary. Get my bag of things out of
the process so you're not love with Derek
but you go to his apartment you would let
me explain that I'm not going to explain
what kind of an explanation could you make
anyway doesn't matter anymore if you're
right it doesn't matter anymore getting
awfully personal but
a wonderful type of Charles Evers is just
like that just like anything else Miss
Yes mind. If I were on
that if you were
a man I'd ask you to step outside so I
had hit me I did. Did he slap I should
say not she slapped you. Know that I
resented me it was because I liked the
novel and I told you so you think you wasted
your time Next you'll attract my only
tragedy is you I'm going far far
away computer and I'm going to write
a book about you I'm going to call
it think he'll in his rectum that's
a very horrible sight don't you fire we're
not afraid to ever try and get in touch
with me because I want no more
of you and that goes for me too.
Just. Flew the coop or you think Steve's
going I think he's going to marry Harris
Aries I'd like to see that little worm I'm
going to or you're going I'm so mad I
could get married so I think I have
to only you want to marry will be
a female that's about all I can say.
And I see Mr Harris your
name on one of the.
Excuse B's. And excuse me I didn't mean
to disturb you and my secretary your
former secretary or I didn't know you
were in the middle of dictation you know
sarcasm is present called of course I
don't have to tell you what I think of
a man who behaves this way with the secretary
to keep out of this job and I'm going
to be married gradually what does where
does that leave my wife how do you suppose
she's going to feel about it she's in
love with you you know you never there's
a bride to go Stephanie anyway you know all
you want to do that I really think you
recruit for your motives a
very obvious you've given me
a lot of grief ever since I married
Stephanie and I came up in
a ten year high to put up your hand to
defend yourself like I'm sure it. Wasn't in
the full fight do you think Stephanie came
up here in the first place because she
wrote a novel in heaven wanted to have
a she didn't back she was afraid it would
hurt your fantasy or wreck your marriage
she wanted to help you
instead. It's grand it's
exciting it's wonderful it's wrong he's
just jealous because I'm. A great guy you
know someday Stephanie is going to be
a better life than you that's my opinion
and you've always bad you that.
Stephanie's number three that and really
get jealous you know you're not going to
get it back she's gone away and it
serves you right I hope I kicked
a little in the air but I down
to the bottom of the world
a very. Know
. I've got to serve you with
these papers what's going to put
a bullet for Mrs Webbe in the bank.
On the run straight let's see. It not feel
disgust but. I didn't notice
that but. I was new secretary.
To watch. Hello Mary.
It was. I guess so.
You see you already are arriving at
the rock you know about the day.
That's funny didn't even invite me
to the wedding stand weenies. On
Me gets married. I'm getting a
divorce you know that's not
a. Water based divorce. I shall apply
here that was to write about she was an
awful nice person she is
a times. I
he's got hiring
a new mail secretary Scott doesn't live in
the building anymore he will back up to
the. Movie enough that
this is rather back.
To the point of all that her
boss makes her to this makes
the room.
Probably. Yes What can I do but
you know I said get out but I
don't understand I'm going to listen to it
because my wife your His wife I'm trying
very desperately not to be Didn't you get
the divorce papers today you're still my
wife until a final agreement that takes
a whole year are you still here I said but
I will get them when you come back here
tomorrow morning at nine o'clock oh come
back you're never five five here again
I'll throw you out on your. I remodeled
secretaries right on the line or right away
you are no see and don't be to have
a time like this why do you take this
apartment anyway because it was the only one
I could find and Mrs Lease was
kind enough to let me have your. I
thought you'd think I was chasing you well
and water breaks but my living here need
cost no embarrassment we can be then lead
in the whole range and change the night
little hello. Exchange polite little
hellos with your friend Harris recently
Elsie was there told me all about you
but you didn't want to have it because
what it might do to me. You know is
refusing a little part of you as
a competitor don't you think I can
compete with you Mr Waterbury I read
a book last night kept me up most of the
night you want to know something yet
you know better than I am but don't tell
anybody because I'll deny it now you
listen to me Mr Owen Waterbury I'm
a human being too and and I have certain
rights and privileges I had an idea for
a book and then you made me lose
a very good secretary one of why don't
you Big Data to me you sure I can take
shorthand all one was a very one
and I would be quick but I'm
a better secretary than you are. All right
through but get this right hand book and
pencil OK and I don't want to hear another
word about our personal problems until I
get this down. That's
copious notes on my new
novel by Stephanie. This will be the
story of a girl who became secretary to
a very egotistical man thought he knew of
one thing there was to know about right
now wait
a minute please you're interrupting my
train of thought. He was attractive.
When ugly sort of really thank the men
would you please stop interrupting me but
but he was he was filled with childish
frustrations and complex this was to use
a silly way Dr Q Oh wait
a minute believe I'm not going to sit
here and take them this is my new book.
Until until he suddenly discovered
he didn't need to write.
A psychiatrist
a spec criers wrist that says it now I'm
insane and I OK but if you promise that
that's always the consumer sentiment but
a lot. You know this books are very interesting
because I don't know if you like of
course not since she loves him
deeply devoted victims they. Say so.
I've. Come to the right
or wrong is your. Book.
I don't know nor that. Their.
Behavior in the world.